User Profile Account, plan, client information and basic settings.
Profil użytkownika Konto, plan, informacje klienta i podstawowe ustawienia.
Step 1 of 14 The top panel shows the profile title and account summary.
Krok 1 z 14 Górny panel pokazuje tytuł profilu i podsumowanie konta.
Step 2 of 14 Return to Menu goes back to the main menu.
Krok 2 z 14 Return to Menu wraca do głównego menu.
Step 3 of 14 Refresh Data reloads current client data.
Krok 3 z 14 Refresh Data odświeża dane klienta.
Step 4 of 14 Cancel Subscription stops subscription renewal.
Krok 4 z 14 Cancel Subscription zatrzymuje odnawianie subskrypcji.
Step 5 of 14 The Client card shows the name and email.
Krok 5 z 14 Karta Client pokazuje nazwę i email.
Step 6 of 14 The Plan card shows the current plan.
Krok 6 z 14 Karta Plan pokazuje aktualny plan.
Step 7 of 14 The Credits card shows remaining credits.
Krok 7 z 14 Credits pokazuje pozostałe kredyty.
Step 8 of 14 The Projects card shows project count and limits.
Krok 8 z 14 Projects pokazuje liczbę projektów i limit.
Step 9 of 14 Client Details contains account, language, status and plan.
Krok 9 z 14 Client Details zawiera konto, język, status i plan.
Step 10 of 14 Subscription Management explains cancellation.
Krok 10 z 14 Subscription Management wyjaśnia anulowanie.
Step 11 of 14 Activated Services shows available services.
Krok 11 z 14 Activated Services pokazuje dostępne usługi.
Step 12 of 14 Enabled Features shows enabled features.
Krok 12 z 14 Enabled Features pokazuje włączone funkcje.
Step 13 of 14 Subscription & Access contains access dates.
Krok 13 z 14 Subscription & Access zawiera daty dostępu.
Step 14 of 14 Bottom cards summarize contact, role and last update.
Krok 14 z 14 Dolne karty podsumowują kontakt, rolę i aktualizację.
Module explained The user knows where to find the module, which parts to use and how to continue working.
Moduł wyjaśniony Użytkownik wie, gdzie znaleźć moduł, które części obsługiwać i jak kontynuować pracę.